<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: News | dentex's blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/categories/news/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://dentex.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-11-10T17:49:58+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://dentex.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Samuele Rini]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changes in YouTube Code]]></title>
    <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-10/changes-in-youtube-code/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-10T17:42:49+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-10/changes-in-youtube-code</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello guys,  <br/>
recently YouTube changed again the code for videos with encrypted signature, so a fix is needed (just for this kind of videos, not for all) for YTD to work properly again.</p>

<p>When the video you&rsquo;re trying to download is affected, all formats appear with a size of <strong>0 B</strong>. Then every format will fail to download.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m aware of the problem, so please avoid sending logcats in regards, but standby for a patch.  <br/>
I&rsquo;ll do it ASAP.</p>

<p>Thanks.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTD v4.8]]></title>
    <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-07/ytd-v4-dot-8/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-07T19:25:22+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-07/ytd-v4-dot-8</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>With this new version, I&rsquo;m limiting the access to the external (removable) sdcard in devices where it&rsquo;s not directly writable (but would need a procedure that I still have to implement) and I&rsquo;m fixing a bug I accidentally introduced in v4.7.</p>

<p>CHANGELOG:</p>

<pre><code> v4.8 - Nov 6 2015
-----------------------------------
[x] always use system file-chooser, on Lollipop or above, with extSdCard not present or not
    (directly) writable
[x] fixed a bug introduced in previous version, causing custom download folder to change into
    private app's data folder 
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTD v4.7]]></title>
    <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-01/ytd-v4-dot-7/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-01T09:32:26+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-11-01/ytd-v4-dot-7</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello,
a new build for YTD is available, moving all features tested into the latest beta into this stable version.</p>

<p>CHANGELOG:</p>

<pre><code> v4.7 - Nov 1 2015
-----------------------------------
[x] new FFmpeg builds (from v2.8) extending support to 64bit CPUs
[x] force FFmpeg's version check when the ROM has been updated
[x] ask the permission to write on the sdcard (on M devices)
[x] fixed filechooser checkbox issue for multiple selection
[x] option to use wi-fi connection only
</code></pre>

<p>A lot of work has to be done, still. Probably development will slow down a bit due to many <em>real life/job</em> commitments, sorry.
I really hope I&rsquo;ll soon be able to post an initial beta from the multi-thread development branch. This will speed-up downloads up to 4X. But unfortunately the feature is not stable nor completed.</p>

<p>In the mean time, stay tuned, follow the XDA threads and, over anything else, I would like to thank everyone that is showing support through the PayPal donations.
I really appreciate that.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTD v4.6]]></title>
    <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-09-24/ytd-v4-dot-6/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-24T11:11:10+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-09-24/ytd-v4-dot-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A new version for YTD is available, with this CHANGELOG:</p>

<pre><code> v4.6 - Sep 24 2015
-----------------------------------
[x] material design for android versions &gt; Lollipop
[x] remove option to embed video preview (now fullscreen only)
[x] better detection of free space on memory storage for some devices
[x] handle the MP4 720p downloads for some very long videos, when file length can't be retrieved
[x] add option for MP3 "download" quality
[x] show correct file size for 480p and 1080p
</code></pre>

<p>Please, report here or on the XDA forum&rsquo;s thread if you see any issues, especially regarding the new theme on Lollipop devices. Thanks!</p>

<p>At the moment, I&rsquo;m working hard on the new (and highly expected) feature of <em>multi-threading</em> downloads.
This will permit to download every file split in 2, 3 or 4 chunks (or 1, like it&rsquo;s now) that will start at the same time, maximizing the network&rsquo;s bandwidth usage and minimizing the hated &ldquo;throttling&rdquo; done by the YouTube servers on certain videos, especially for some qualities.</p>

<p>From some initial tests, the new feature seems to go pretty well, with a minor impact on the app&rsquo;s weight (although this exists anyway).</p>

<p>Stay tuned for the next beta.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTD v4.5.1]]></title>
    <link href="http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-06-19/ytd-v4-dot-5-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T11:45:17+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://dentex.github.io/blog/2015-06-19/ytd-v4-dot-5-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A new <em>maintenance</em> build for YTD is available, with just some bug-fixing and improvements.</p>

<p>Changelog:</p>

<pre><code> v4.5.1 - Jun 19 2015
-----------------------------------
[x] do not fail muxing when 1080p and 480p downloads coexist into the Dashboard
    (thanks scandiun @XDA)
[x] do again broken mux operations using the pause/resume menu item
[x] support JuiceSSH to send remote downloads
[x] proper check to manually mux only .mp4 with .m4a and .webm with .ogg streams
</code></pre>

<p>Direct <a href="http://dentex.github.io/files/apk/latest/dentex.youtube.downloader.apk">APK link</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
